gottadeal.com 2015-11-30

# Privacy Policy - GottaDeal.com

* * *

_Posted September 23, 2014 by GottaDeal.com Staff_ **Privacy Policy Table of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * About Information Posted on Forum
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

 **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the GottaDeal.com website. On some pages, you can send messages to us, register for the forum and register to receive materials via e-mail or traditional mail. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Address, E-Mail Address, Phone Number, etc...

 **The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself to conduct normal site business only. We do not share this information with outside parties unless explicity stated or agreed to by you.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our Daily Deal Update deal alert e-mails.  Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form for this service.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an affiliate partner that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number visitors clicked on a specific link, or that Z number of visitors are subscribed to our mailing list, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **About Information Posted on Forum**

Should you choose to register for the forum and create posts, be aware that anything you post could be viewable to any site visitor, and you are consenting to any or all of this information being used for other site purposes. By posting you agree to not hold the site responsible for any unauthorized use of this information by an outside visitor.

 **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us, or if on the forum, by examining your user profile and options. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (414) 375-2359 or contact us using the form available here on the site. 

|  | 

| 

| 

---|---  

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

|
